{
  "deck": {
    "id": "2",
    "name": "Sample Generated Deck",
    "filename": "mock-01-data.json",
    "tags": [
      "generated",
      "test",
      "demo"
    ],
    "cards": {
      "q1": {
        "front": "What is the answer to question 1?",
        "back": "The answer to question 1 is 2.",
        "tags": [
          "geography",
          "language",
          "medium"
        ],
        "level": 5,
        "id": 1
      },
      "q2": {
        "front": "What is the answer to question 2?",
        "back": "The answer to question 2 is 4.",
        "tags": [
          "medium"
        ],
        "level": 3,
        "id": 2
      },
      "q3": {
        "front": "What is the answer to question 3?",
        "back": "The answer to question 3 is 6.",
        "tags": [
          "math",
          "history"
        ],
        "level": 1,
        "id": 3
      },
      "q4": {
        "front": "What is the answer to question 4?",
        "back": "The answer to question 4 is 8.",
        "tags": [
          "medium",
          "history",
          "math"
        ],
        "level": 5,
        "id": 4
      },
      "q5": {
        "front": "What is the answer to question 5?",
        "back": "The answer to question 5 is 10.",
        "tags": [
          "easy",
          "science"
        ],
        "level": 4,
        "id": 5
      },
      "q6": {
        "front": "What is the answer to question 6?",
        "back": "The answer to question 6 is 12.",
        "tags": [
          "easy"
        ],
        "level": 2,
        "id": 6
      },
      "q7": {
        "front": "What is the answer to question 7?",
        "back": "The answer to question 7 is 14.",
        "tags": [
          "medium",
          "history"
        ],
        "level": 2,
        "id": 7
      },
      "q8": {
        "front": "What is the answer to question 8?",
        "back": "The answer to question 8 is 16.",
        "tags": [
          "science",
          "history"
        ],
        "level": 0,
        "id": 8
      },
      "q9": {
        "front": "What is the answer to question 9?",
        "back": "The answer to question 9 is 18.",
        "tags": [
          "geography",
          "easy",
          "history"
        ],
        "level": 1,
        "id": 9
      },
      "q10": {
        "front": "What is the answer to question 10?",
        "back": "The answer to question 10 is 20.",
        "tags": [
          "easy",
          "history"
        ],
        "level": 5,
        "id": 10
      },
      "q11": {
        "front": "What is the answer to question 11?",
        "back": "The answer to question 11 is 22.",
        "tags": [
          "hard",
          "science"
        ],
        "level": 0,
        "id": 11
      },
      "q12": {
        "front": "What is the answer to question 12?",
        "back": "The answer to question 12 is 24.",
        "tags": [
          "language",
          "hard"
        ],
        "level": 0,
        "id": 12
      },
      "q13": {
        "front": "What is the answer to question 13?",
        "back": "The answer to question 13 is 26.",
        "tags": [
          "history",
          "medium"
        ],
        "level": 1,
        "id": 13
      },
      "q14": {
        "front": "What is the answer to question 14?",
        "back": "The answer to question 14 is 28.",
        "tags": [
          "hard",
          "medium",
          "geography"
        ],
        "level": 3,
        "id": 14
      },
      "q15": {
        "front": "What is the answer to question 15?",
        "back": "The answer to question 15 is 30.",
        "tags": [
          "history"
        ],
        "level": 4,
        "id": 15
      },
      "q16": {
        "front": "What is the answer to question 16?",
        "back": "The answer to question 16 is 32.",
        "tags": [
          "hard",
          "medium"
        ],
        "level": 4,
        "id": 16
      },
      "q17": {
        "front": "What is the answer to question 17?",
        "back": "The answer to question 17 is 34.",
        "tags": [
          "history",
          "math",
          "medium"
        ],
        "level": 5,
        "id": 17
      },
      "q18": {
        "front": "What is the answer to question 18?",
        "back": "The answer to question 18 is 36.",
        "tags": [
          "geography"
        ],
        "level": 1,
        "id": 18
      },
      "q19": {
        "front": "What is the answer to question 19?",
        "back": "The answer to question 19 is 38.",
        "tags": [
          "geography"
        ],
        "level": 0,
        "id": 19
      },
      "q20": {
        "front": "What is the answer to question 20?",
        "back": "The answer to question 20 is 40.",
        "tags": [
          "easy",
          "language"
        ],
        "level": 4,
        "id": 20
      },
      "q21": {
        "front": "What is the answer to question 21?",
        "back": "The answer to question 21 is 42.",
        "tags": [
          "history",
          "geography"
        ],
        "level": 4,
        "id": 21
      },
      "q22": {
        "front": "What is the answer to question 22?",
        "back": "The answer to question 22 is 44.",
        "tags": [
          "hard",
          "geography",
          "history"
        ],
        "level": 4,
        "id": 22
      },
      "q23": {
        "front": "What is the answer to question 23?",
        "back": "The answer to question 23 is 46.",
        "tags": [
          "history",
          "hard",
          "math"
        ],
        "level": 5,
        "id": 23
      },
      "q24": {
        "front": "What is the answer to question 24?",
        "back": "The answer to question 24 is 48.",
        "tags": [
          "history",
          "hard"
        ],
        "level": 1,
        "id": 24
      },
      "q25": {
        "front": "What is the answer to question 25?",
        "back": "The answer to question 25 is 50.",
        "tags": [
          "geography",
          "medium",
          "math"
        ],
        "level": 1,
        "id": 25
      },
      "q26": {
        "front": "What is the answer to question 26?",
        "back": "The answer to question 26 is 52.",
        "tags": [
          "history"
        ],
        "level": 1,
        "id": 26
      },
      "q27": {
        "front": "What is the answer to question 27?",
        "back": "The answer to question 27 is 54.",
        "tags": [
          "medium"
        ],
        "level": 3,
        "id": 27
      },
      "q28": {
        "front": "What is the answer to question 28?",
        "back": "The answer to question 28 is 56.",
        "tags": [
          "math"
        ],
        "level": 2,
        "id": 28
      },
      "q29": {
        "front": "What is the answer to question 29?",
        "back": "The answer to question 29 is 58.",
        "tags": [
          "science"
        ],
        "level": 5,
        "id": 29
      },
      "q30": {
        "front": "What is the answer to question 30?",
        "back": "The answer to question 30 is 60.",
        "tags": [
          "hard",
          "math",
          "history"
        ],
        "level": 0,
        "id": 30
      },
      "q31": {
        "front": "What is the answer to question 31?",
        "back": "The answer to question 31 is 62.",
        "tags": [
          "easy"
        ],
        "level": 0,
        "id": 31
      },
      "q32": {
        "front": "What is the answer to question 32?",
        "back": "The answer to question 32 is 64.",
        "tags": [
          "easy",
          "history"
        ],
        "level": 1,
        "id": 32
      },
      "q33": {
        "front": "What is the answer to question 33?",
        "back": "The answer to question 33 is 66.",
        "tags": [
          "math"
        ],
        "level": 2,
        "id": 33
      },
      "q34": {
        "front": "What is the answer to question 34?",
        "back": "The answer to question 34 is 68.",
        "tags": [
          "math",
          "hard",
          "geography"
        ],
        "level": 2,
        "id": 34
      },
      "q35": {
        "front": "What is the answer to question 35?",
        "back": "The answer to question 35 is 70.",
        "tags": [
          "hard",
          "easy",
          "medium"
        ],
        "level": 1,
        "id": 35
      },
      "q36": {
        "front": "What is the answer to question 36?",
        "back": "The answer to question 36 is 72.",
        "tags": [
          "history",
          "geography"
        ],
        "level": 1,
        "id": 36
      },
      "q37": {
        "front": "What is the answer to question 37?",
        "back": "The answer to question 37 is 74.",
        "tags": [
          "easy"
        ],
        "level": 2,
        "id": 37
      },
      "q38": {
        "front": "What is the answer to question 38?",
        "back": "The answer to question 38 is 76.",
        "tags": [
          "math"
        ],
        "level": 5,
        "id": 38
      },
      "q39": {
        "front": "What is the answer to question 39?",
        "back": "The answer to question 39 is 78.",
        "tags": [
          "medium",
          "hard",
          "language"
        ],
        "level": 5,
        "id": 39
      },
      "q40": {
        "front": "What is the answer to question 40?",
        "back": "The answer to question 40 is 80.",
        "tags": [
          "science",
          "hard",
          "easy"
        ],
        "level": 2,
        "id": 40
      },
      "q41": {
        "front": "What is the answer to question 41?",
        "back": "The answer to question 41 is 82.",
        "tags": [
          "history"
        ],
        "level": 1,
        "id": 41
      },
      "q42": {
        "front": "What is the answer to question 42?",
        "back": "The answer to question 42 is 84.",
        "tags": [
          "science",
          "easy",
          "medium"
        ],
        "level": 2,
        "id": 42
      },
      "q43": {
        "front": "What is the answer to question 43?",
        "back": "The answer to question 43 is 86.",
        "tags": [
          "language"
        ],
        "level": 5,
        "id": 43
      },
      "q44": {
        "front": "What is the answer to question 44?",
        "back": "The answer to question 44 is 88.",
        "tags": [
          "language",
          "geography",
          "math"
        ],
        "level": 3,
        "id": 44
      },
      "q45": {
        "front": "What is the answer to question 45?",
        "back": "The answer to question 45 is 90.",
        "tags": [
          "hard",
          "history",
          "language"
        ],
        "level": 0,
        "id": 45
      },
      "q46": {
        "front": "What is the answer to question 46?",
        "back": "The answer to question 46 is 92.",
        "tags": [
          "math"
        ],
        "level": 1,
        "id": 46
      },
      "q47": {
        "front": "What is the answer to question 47?",
        "back": "The answer to question 47 is 94.",
        "tags": [
          "science"
        ],
        "level": 4,
        "id": 47
      },
      "q48": {
        "front": "What is the answer to question 48?",
        "back": "The answer to question 48 is 96.",
        "tags": [
          "easy",
          "history"
        ],
        "level": 3,
        "id": 48
      },
      "q49": {
        "front": "What is the answer to question 49?",
        "back": "The answer to question 49 is 98.",
        "tags": [
          "geography"
        ],
        "level": 2,
        "id": 49
      },
      "q50": {
        "front": "What is the answer to question 50?",
        "back": "The answer to question 50 is 100.",
        "tags": [
          "science",
          "math"
        ],
        "level": 1,
        "id": 50
      }
    }
  }
}